Who is the best person to give you advice when it‘s time to give your wardrobe a makeover?
当需要对衣橱进行大改造的时候，谁是你提供建议的最佳人选呢？
You might turn to your friends for some feedback and fashion tips - let’s face it: they know you best and can be honest about which colours clash - and which outfit makes you look smouldering!
你可能会向你的朋友寻求一些反馈和时尚建议——让我们面对现实吧：他们最了解你，并且能够诚实地告诉你哪些颜色会不协调——以及哪套服装能让你看起来魅力十足。
However, for someone like me, who‘s not a follower of fashion and has a more practical dress sense, I don’t need help - it‘s just jeans or... jeans!
然而，对于像我这样不追随时尚潮流，更注重实用着装风格的人来说，我不需要帮助——穿的就是牛仔裤或者……还是牛仔裤！
But for people who care about their appearance, they can now get some trustworthy advice with the aid of technology.
但对于那些在乎自己外表的人来说，他们现在可以在科技帮助下获得一些可靠的建议。
Of course, using social media is a good way to discuss fashion dilemmas with your friends, but this sometimes brings in too much conflicting advice - and opinions that are sometimes brutal!
当然，使用社交媒体是和朋友讨论时尚两难困境的好方法，但这有时会带来太多相互矛盾的建议——而且这些意见有时还很令人不快！
That’s why one woman has developed an app to help women crowdsource advice from stylists and sister fashionistas in a safe, troll-free environment.
这就是为什么有一位女士开发了一款应用程序，帮助女性在一个安全、没有网络喷子的环境中从造型师和时尚达人姐妹们那里收集建议。
Sophia Matveeva‘s Style Counsel app allows users wanting advice on an outfit to post a photo and receive “yes” or “no” answers from other users, or more detailed advice from vetted fashion stylists and bloggers very quickly.
索菲亚·马特韦耶娃的“时尚顾问”应用程序允许想要获得服装搭配建议的用户上传一张照片，然后很快就能收到其他用户给出的“行”或“不行”的回答，或者从经过审核的时尚造型师和博主那里获得更详细的建议。
According to Matthew Wall, BBC Technology of Business editor, this is a growing business, with several new apps such as AskAnna, Mallzee and StyleDotMe all offering young women tips on suitable and fashionable clothes to wear.
据BBC商业科技编辑马修·沃尔称，这是一个正在蓬勃发展的业务，有几个新的应用程序，如AskAnna、Mallzee和StyleDotMe，都为年轻女性提供关于适合且时尚的服装穿着建议。
There‘s also a website called EyeFitU which finds clothes to fit your figure.
还有一个名为EyeFitU的网站，它可以找到适合你身材的衣服。
Its chief executive, Isabelle Ohnemus, says there are no international standards in clothes sizes but she explains “We can set up your size profile in a few seconds with 80% accuracy just knowing your gender, height, weight and age”.
其首席执行官伊莎贝尔·奥内穆斯说，服装尺码没有国际标准，但她解释说：“我们只需知道你的性别、身高、体重和年龄，就能在几秒钟内以80%的准确率为你建立尺码档案。”
This information is used to search different retailers and find clothes that suit your actual shape.
这些信息被用来搜索不同的零售商，找到适合你实际身材的衣服。
And the internet giant, Amazon, has also developed a camera that links to a ’style check‘ function that compares photos and gives its algorithmically-derived opinion of which outfit is better, based on fit, colour, style and current fashion trends.
互联网巨头亚马逊也开发了一款相机，它与“风格检查”功能相连，可以比较照片，并根据合身程度、颜色、风格和当前的时尚趋势，给出其通过算法得出的哪套服装更好的意见。
But is technology making fashion advice a bit impersonal?
但科技是否让时尚建议变得有点没有人情味呢？
Sophia Matveeva admits that women especially are social animals, and “AI will never stop us from communicating with each other... girls always want validation from the cool girl at school.”
索菲亚·马特韦耶娃承认，女性尤其是社交性动物，而且“人工智能永远无法阻止我们相互交流......女孩们总是希望得到学校里那个很酷的女孩的认可。”
But for me: I’d probably turn to an app full of strangers first to get some discreet fashion advice.
但对我来说：我可能首先会去一个满是陌生人的应用程序获得一些不引人注意的时尚建议。